（中央咖啡廳）
Monica? Hey, can I borrow the Porsche?
摩妮卡，我可以借你的保時捷嗎？
- Okay. - All right!
-好的 -太好了！
But what is it not?
有什麼「不准」的呢？
A place to entertain my lady friends.
不准在車上和我女性朋友玩樂
- And what else is it not? - A place to eat spaghetti.
-還有什麼呢？ -不准在車上吃意大利面
Very good. What do you need it for anyway?
非常好，你為什麼會需要開車呢？
The Powerball lottery is up to 300 million..
超級大樂透獎金已經累積到三億了
- and they don't sell tickets here. - So you're driving up to Connecticut?
-但是這裡沒有在賣彩券 -所以你要開車到康乃狄克州買？
Yeah, Connecticut. Not West Virginia.
對，康乃狄克州，不是西維吉尼亞
Maybe I'll drive you up there. I'd like to buy some tickets myself.
或許我可以開車載你去 我自己也想買幾張彩券
Yeah, with Chandler not getting paid, we could really use $300 million.
錢德現在沒有在賺錢 三億對我們可是會很好用的
Yes, because if I was at my old job, we'd say, "300 million? No, thank you."
是的，因為如果我還是在老工作 我們會說「要三億嗎？不用，謝謝」
- Will you get me tickets too? - Yeah, me too.
-你可以幫我買嗎？ -對啊，我也要
- Sure. - I have an idea.
-當然 -我有個點子
Why don't we all pitch in 50 bucks, we'll pool our money together..
我們可以各出資五十塊 把錢集合起來
- and then if we win, we'll split it. - That's a great idea!
-然後如果我們中獎，我們就平分 -好主意！
No, thanks.
不用，謝了
- You don't wanna win the lottery? - Sure I do.
-你不想要中樂透嗎？ -我當然想
I also want to be king of my own country..
我還想當國王咧
and find out what happened to Amelia Earhart.
探索第一位飛越大西洋的女飛行員 是怎麼了
- Still on Amelia Earhart? - The woman just vanished!
-還在想女飛行員嗎？ -那女人就這樣消失了！
Seriously, you don't want in on this?
說真的，你真的不要加入嗎？
No. Do you know what your odds are of winning the lottery?
不要，你們知道 中樂透的機率有多大嗎？
I mean, you have a better chance of being struck by lightning 42 times.
比你被閃電打到四十二次的機率還小
But there's six of us, so we'd only have to get struck 7 times.
但是我們有六個人 所以我們只需要被打到七次
I like those odds!
我喜歡這種機率！
Seriously, you guys, I can't believe you're gonna spend $250 on the lottery.
真的，你們，我不敢相信你們會 願意花兩百塊錢在樂透上面
I mean, that's such a bunch of boo-hockey.
這實在太唬爛了吧？
I'll ask.
我來問
"Boo-hockey"?
「唬爛」？
Oh, we think Emma's about to start talking..
我們認為艾□已經快要開始說話了
so we're trying to be careful about what words we use in front of her.
所以在她面前我們會小心用字
So get ready to hear a lot of boo-hockey..
所以準備好 你們會聽到很多的「胡說」…
gosh darn it and brother pucker.
「討厭」還有「惹人煩」等等
How do you know she's gonna start talking?
你怎麼知道她要開始說話了呢？
When I talk to her, I almost feel like she understands what I'm saying.
當我跟她說話時，我幾乎可以感覺到 她聽得懂我在說什麼
Kind of like Joey.
有點像喬伊
What's that now?
你說什麼？
The One With The Lottery
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
God, look at all these tickets. It's so exciting.
天啊，瞧瞧這全部的彩券 真是緊張刺激
I haven't won anything since sixth grade.
自從六年級後 我就沒有贏過任何東西了
Pie-eating contest?
吃派大賽呢？
You assume because I was heavy that's the only way I could win something?
因為我很胖，你就以為 那是我唯一能贏的比賽嗎？？
No, I saw a picture of you covered in blueberries.
不，我看過你埋在藍莓派裡面的照片
- That was a good day. - Yeah.
-那時候真快樂 -是啊
- They're towing your car! - I'm parked in a garage on Morton.
-他們在拖你的車！ -我停在車庫裡面
They're towing a car.
他們正在拖一輛車
And I am seeing spots.
我眼花了
Ross, you don't have Emma! Rachel, you don't have Emma!
羅斯，你沒有在帶艾□！ 瑞秋，你也沒有在帶艾□！
- Where's Emma? Who has Emma? - Joey, relax.
-艾□呢？艾□誰在帶呢？ -喬伊，別緊張
My mother picked her up two hours ago. You were there.
我媽兩小時前來帶走她了 你也在場啊
- I was? - Yes, and you talked to her.
-有嗎？ -是的，而且你還跟她說話
- I did? - She dropped off a casserole.
-我有嗎？ -她還帶來了砂鍋菜來
Oh, yeah, the casserole lady.
喔，對啊，那個砂鍋女士
Did you come by to watch us win the big bucks?
你過來看我們中大獎的嗎？
Yeah. And then I figured after you win, we can all go out to the balcony..
是啊，然後我想在你們中獎後 我們全部到陽台上…
and see a night rainbow with gremlins dancing on top of it.
看有小精靈在跳舞的夜間彩虹
Don't touch the phone! I'll get it!
別接電話！我來接！
- You think he washed his hands? - Hello?
-你覺得他有洗手嗎？ -哈囉？
- Hey, Charlie, what do you know? - What's going on?
-嘿，查理，有什麼消息？ -怎麼回事？
Chandler's supposed to find out if he's getting a job at his agency.
錢德想知道他有沒有得到 公司內部的一個工作機會
But out of 15 interns, they're only hiring three.
但在十五名實習生中 他們只聘請三個人
- Tough odds. - Yeah.
-機率真小 -是啊
If only it were a sure thing like your 24-state lottery.
還真希望能像你們二十四州 聯合彩券的機率一樣高
Yeah, look who's coming around!
是啊，瞧瞧誰想通了！
Damn it. All right, call me when you know more.
該死，好啦，有更多消息再告訴我
- Did you get it? - One of the slots got filled.
-你有得到嗎？ -一個名額已經被佔了
- By you? - Sense the tone.
-被你嗎？ -注意我的語氣
- No, that kid Nate got it. - Oh, I hate that guy.
-不是，一個叫做奈特的小子 -喔，我討厭那個人
I mean, come on, kid, pull up your pants!
我是說，真是的，小子 穿上褲子吧！
Well, there's two spots left, right?
還有兩個名額不是嗎？
Yeah. I mean, I want this so much. I wanna get one.
是啊，我真的好想要，我想要被錄取
I want my friend Charlie to get one.
也希望我朋友查理被錄取
Except I don't care about Charlie.
其實我不是很在乎查理
- Hey, you guys. - Hey!
-嘿，你們好 -嘿！
You are not gonna believe this. I just saw my psychic..
你們不會相信的 我剛剛去找過我的算命師
and she said I was definitely gonna win the lottery tonight!
她說我今晚一定會中樂透！
I thought we could use some extra luck..
我想要增加好運…
so I brought a wishbone home from work.
所以從餐廳帶幸運骨頭回來
A psychic and a wishbone? Guys, give someone else a chance.
算命師跟幸運骨頭？ 拜託給別人一點機會吧
- All right, who wants to do it? - Can I?
-好了，誰要來做呢？ -我可以嗎？
Vegetarians never get to do the wishbone.
素食者從來就沒有機會玩幸運骨頭
It's really not fair. Just because we don't eat the meat..
真是不公平，我們只是不吃肉
doesn't mean we don't like to play with the carcasses.
不代表我們不喜歡玩骨頭
All right. Rach?
好了，瑞秋呢？
I don't want that turkey smell all over my hands.
我不想要雙手沾滿火雞的味道
I'll do it! It'll get the casserole stink off of mine.
我來，我要把砂鍋菜的味道蓋過去
- I hope I win. - Well, it doesn't really matter.
-希望我會贏 -嗯，沒有關係
You're both wishing for the same thing.
你們的願望是一樣的
I can't tell you what I'm wishing for, or else, you know, it won't come true.
我不能告訴你我許什麼願 要不然不會實現的
Right. But we know what you're wishing for.
對，但是我們都知道你許什麼願
- I can't really say. - I understand.
-我不能說 -我瞭解
But you're wishing for what we think, aren't you?
但是你許的願 跟我們想的一樣，不是嗎？
I'm not really comfortable with these questions!
我真的很不喜歡這些問題！
- Please! - Just do it!
-拜託！ -趕快做！
Okay. One, two, three.
好的，一，二，三
I won! Hey!
我贏了！嘿！
You know what? I'm sure your wish is gonna come true.
你們知道嗎？我確定 你們的願望會成真
But, you guys, just in case, maybe a genie will come out if we rub this lamp.
但是，為了以防萬一 我們來磨擦這個燈，或許精靈會出現
That thing gets hot!
那東西好燙！
Ross, just keep making your jokes.
羅斯，繼續說你的笑話吧
How are you gonna feel if we actually do win?
如果我們中了 你有什麼感受？
- You're not gonna win. - I know the odds are against us..
-你們不會中的 -我知道機率很小
but somebody has to win, and it could be us. And then how you gonna feel?
但是總是有人會中，可能就是我們 然後你會覺得如何呢？
We're gonna be like, "Everybody, let's take our helicopters up to the Cape."
我們會說「大家開直升機去海角玩吧」
And you're gonna be all, like, "Oh, I can't, guys.
而你只能說喔，我不行…
I'll have to meet you up there. I gotta gas up the Hyundai."
我們到那邊碰面好了 我先幫我的車子加滿油
Okay, I've heard myself on tape, and I sound nothing like that.
好了，我聽過自己在錄音帶裡的聲音 我聽起來根本不像那樣
I can see the headline now: "Lottery Winners' Friend..
我可以想像頭條新聞是 彩券贏家的朋友…
Filled With Regret, Eats Own Arm."
充滿懊悔，吃下自己的手臂
Why would I eat my own arm?
我為什麼要吃自己的手臂？
Well, you wouldn't, but we own the paper. We can print whatever we want.
你當然不會，但是報紙是我們的 我們愛怎麼寫就怎麼寫
You know what? I'm gonna throw in 50 bucks for you.
你知道嗎？我幫你出五十塊好了
- Why? - Because I know that you think..
-為什麼？ -因為我知道你認為…
that the lottery is boo-hockey..
樂透是很唬爛的東西
but we're all here, and we're gonna watch the numbers and have fun.
但是我們全都聚在一起 看開獎，會很好玩的
And you're my brother, and I want you to be a part of this.
而你是我哥哥，我希望你能參與
You don't have to do that. I mean, I'll pay for myself.
你不需要這樣做的，我可以自己出錢
But just the fact that you want me to have fun with you guys, that's so sweet.
但是你想要讓我跟你們一起同樂 真的是太窩心了
Come here.
過來
Get a room.
去開個房間吧
So now that you're in, what are you gonna do if we win?
那既然你已經加入了 要是中獎，你要做什麼事呢？
- I don't know. I'll probably just invest it. - Calm down.
-我不知道，或許投資吧 -對，要冷靜
Seriously, that's your fantasy? To invest it?
正經點，你的夢想呢？投資？
Oh, I'm sorry. Did I say, "invest it"? I meant, "Be cool and piss it all away."
喔，我很抱歉，我是說投資嗎？ 我的意思是「快樂的全部花光光」
I know! We should pool all our money and buy the Knicks!
我知道了！我們該把全部的錢湊起來 買下尼克隊！
I don't really care about the Knicks.
我不是很在乎尼克隊
You will when I pick you as starting forward.
如果我選你當前鋒，你就會了
You would do that? I never get picked!
你會那樣做嗎？我從沒有被選上！
I'm not sure a sports team is the way to go.
我不確定球隊會是正確的選擇
You won't let me buy the Knicks? I can't believe you're taking this away.
你不讓我買尼克隊嗎？ 我不敢相信你要打碎我的夢想
You're right, it has been your dream for over 15 seconds.
你說的對，這個夢想 已經有十五秒之久了
How long until they announce the numbers, Mommy?
他們還有多久才會公佈號碼呢？媽咪
I'll take this one too. "Mommy"?
這個也讓我來 什麼「媽咪」啊？
Oh, I've gotten into the habit of calling Rachel..
喔，我已經習慣叫瑞秋…
"Mommy" when we're around Emma.
「媽咪」，只要是艾□在場
Which I now realize we are not.
我現在發現她並不在
I'm hoping that if she hears it enough, it'll be her first word.
我希望如果她聽久了 這將成為她第一句會說的話
Although if we're gonna do that, we should probably call me "Daddy" too.
如果我們真的要這樣做 你也應該叫我「爹地」才對
I like that, Daddy.
我喜歡，爹地
I was just talking about Rachel.
我只是在說瑞秋
Is Daddy getting angry?
爹地生氣了嗎？
Is Daddy gonna spank me?
爹地要打我嗎？
Well, that depends.
嗯，要看情況
Have you been a bad..? No, I can't.
你是不是壞…？ 不，我演不下去了
Hello? Hello? Hey, Charlie. Did anybody else hear?
哈囉？哈囉？嘿，查理 還有其他人知道嗎？
What? Susan got it? How?
什麼？蘇珊拿到了？怎麼會呢？
Oh, man, I would've slept with him!
喔，天啊，早知道我也跟他上床！
All right, bye.
好了，拜
Dude, I'm sorry. But hey, there's one spot left, right?
老兄，我很抱歉 但是，還有一個名額不是嗎？
- Well, Charlie's gonna get that. - Hey, don't say that.
-查理會得到的 -嘿，別那樣說
You've got just as good a chance of getting that job.
你也有機會得到那工作的
He is the boss' son.
他是老闆的兒子
- Come on, lottery! - Yeah!
-好了，樂透！ -是啊！
- It starts in, like,20 minutes. - Okay, here we go.
-再大概二十分鐘就開獎了 -好了，我們來吧
We need to sort through the tickets quickly to see if we've won.
我們需要快點分配這些彩券來對獎
So does anybody have any ideas how to organize this?
有人有什麼主意要怎麼安排嗎？
Okay, how about this:
好的，看看這樣如何
We divide them into six groups of 40.
我們分成六組各四十張
The remaining 10 can be read by whoever finishes first.
剩下的十張就由先對完的人來對
- I have another idea. - I'm sorry, idea time is over.
-我還有一個主意 -很抱歉，提議時間已經過了
- Well, are all the tickets in the bowl? - Yeah.
-所有的彩券都在碗裡了嗎？ -是的
- What about the ones on the nightstand? - There are no tickets there.
-那床頭櫃上面的那些呢？ -那邊沒有彩券
Yes, there are. I just saw them a few minutes ago.
是的，那邊有 我幾分鐘前才看到
No, you didn't. You must be mistaken.
不對，沒有，你看錯了
- There are 20 tickets on the nightstand. - Chandler, sense the tone.
-床頭櫃上有二十張彩券 -錢德，注意我的語氣
Well, well, well. Look what Mommy found.
喔，喔，喔，瞧瞧媽咪找到了什麼
Okay, fine. I bought 20 extra tickets for me and Chandler.
好啦，我幫自己跟錢德多買了二十張
The psychic also said that I would be betrayed.
算命的還說我會被朋友給背叛
I can't believe this. I thought we were all in this together.
我不敢相信，我以為我們是一起的
- Hey, you just got in five minutes ago! - Three minutes ago!
-嘿，你五分鐘前才加入的！ -是三分鐘！
I don't know why that's important.
我不知道那有什麼重要的
I was with you the whole time. When did you even get those?
我一直都跟你在一起 你是什麼時候買的？
When you were reading the dirty magazines without taking off the plastic.
當你在看未拆封的色情書刊的時候
I'll show you how.
我再分給你看
Okay. Well, Monica, suppose one of your special tickets wins?
好了，摩妮卡 假設你的彩券中獎了怎麼辦？
How are you gonna feel when you win and lose your friends?
你覺得中了彩券 失去了朋友又怎樣？
Please. If I win the lottery, you guys are not gonna leave me.
拜託，如果我中獎了 你們才不會離開我
Someone gave me muffins last week, and I couldn't get rid of you for three days!
有人上星期給我一堆鬆餅 害我整整三天都被你們騷擾！
Chandler, would you just tell her what she did was wrong?
錢德，你可以告訴她這是不對的嗎？
She's right. You shouldn't have bought tickets just for us.
她說的對，你不應該 幫我們兩個另買彩券
Let me finish.
讓我說完
However, it doesn't look like I'm gonna get this job..
然而，看起來我好像得不到這份工作了
so I can't afford to have principles. So screw you! The tickets are ours!
所以我不能太有原則 去你們的！彩券是我們的！
There's the man I married.
這才是我嫁的好男人
All right. Believe me, if you win the lottery..
好了，相信我，如果你們中獎了
it's the last you're gonna hear from us.
你們就跟我們不是朋友了
Fine. Don't be my friends. I'll buy new friends.
無所謂，不要當我的朋友就算了 我會買新朋友的
Yeah, and then I'll pay for their plastic surgery so they look just like you!
是的，我還會付錢讓他們動整形手術 讓他們看起來跟你們一模一樣！
You know what? I want my share of the tickets.
你知道嗎？我要拿回我的份
I want my tickets too! And I'm buying the Knicks!
我也要拿回我的彩券！ 而且我要買下尼克隊！
And Steffi Graf!
還有葛拉芙！
Cool. Then I want mine too! And if I win..
太好了，那我也要拿回我的！ 而且如果我中獎…
I'm gonna put it all into a very low-yield bond!
我要拿全部的錢去買低利公債！
No. You guys, we gotta keep all the tickets together.
不行，我們必須要 把全部的彩券集合在一起
No. No, we should divide them up..
不，我們應該分一分
and I should get extra because we used my car!
而且我應該多分點 因為是開我的車買的！
Hey! Hey! If anybody gets extra tickets, it should be me!
嘿！嘿！如果有人可以多拿一些 那個人應該是我！
- This whole thing was my idea! - Yeah. Thanks for inventing the lottery!
-這整件事都是我想出來的！ -是啊，謝謝你發明樂透！
Just give them to me, and I'll split them up!
把彩券給我，我來分！
Hey, hey!
嘿，嘿！
God, I can't take it anymore! I'm putting an end to this!
天啊，我再也受不了了！ 我來結束這一切！
- Okay, if she jumps, I get her tickets! - Wait, no, no! Hey!
-如果她跳樓了，她的彩券就是我的！ -等等，不！嘿！
If we're not doing this together, we're not doing it at all.
如果我們不要一起合資 那我們就什麼都不要
- Say goodbye to your tickets. - No! No! No!
-跟你們的彩券說再見吧 -不！不！不！
Do not come any closer!
不要再靠近過來了！
Can I come a little bit closer? Valuable things are getting squished.
我可以再靠近一點點嗎？ 我的寶貝被壓到了
Now, what's more important, your friends or money?
現在，什麼比較重要？ 朋友還是錢？
- Friends! - Money!
-朋友！ -錢！
Friends.
朋友
Hey, Monica, what about your extra tickets?
嘿，摩妮卡，那你其它的彩券呢？
They're all in there.
全都在裡面了
- Even these five that I hid in my bra. - Monica!
-還有我內衣藏的這五張 -摩妮卡！
Okay. Good. You guys were so scared.
好的，很好，你們都嚇壞了
There is no way I was gonna dump this..
我根本不可能會丟掉這些…
God! No!
天啊！不！
I think I broke your bowl.
我想我把你的碗摔破了
Go! Go! Go!
快、快、快！
What a beautiful night to be running around the street, looking for tickets.
到街上去找彩券 真是美好的夜晚啊
And the wind sure made it fun.
而且被風一吹就更有趣了
- Phoebe, we lost half of them. - So what?
-菲比，有一半不見了 -那又如何呢？
Monica, we have the winning ticket.
摩妮卡，我們還是會中獎的
My psychic said I was gonna win, remember?
算命師說我會中獎的，記得嗎？
Weird your psychic didn't mention anything about the scary pigeon.
奇怪的是 算命師並沒有算到可怕的鴿子
As a matter of fact, she said that's how I'm going to die.
事實上她是有說過 我會那樣死去
So excuse me for being a little skittish.
所以，原諒我有點被嚇到
There's two messages. This could be from work.
有兩通留言，可能是工作的消息
- Oh, play them. - Okay. Here we go.
-喔，放來聽聽 -好了，來了
Hello. This is the pigeon from the balcony calling to apologize.
哈囉，我是陽台上的鴿子 打電話過來道歉的
I shouldn't have knocked the tickets out of the pretty lady's hand.
我不應該把彩券 從那個漂亮小姐手中弄翻
It was all my fault. Not hers. Bye.
這全是我的錯，不關她的事，拜
Well, I bet that was very hard for him to do.
嗯，我敢說要他這樣道歉 一定很難
Hey, Chandler, it's Charlie.
嘿，錢德，我是查理
This is it.
就是這個了
Listen, it turns out I got the last spot.
聽著，結果是我拿到最後的名額
I'm really sorry, man. It was a lot of fun working with you.
我很抱歉，老兄 很高興跟你共事過
Give me a call if you want.
再打電話給我吧
Gosh, I ' m so sorry, honey.
天啊，我很難過，親愛的
Sorry, Chandler.
真替你難過，錢德
It is so unfair. It's like that time they promoted Saundra over me at work.
這真是不公平，這就像那次 他們升珊卓，而不是我一樣
Was she related to Ralph Lauren?
她跟洛夫羅倫有親戚關係嗎？
No, she was just much better at her job than me.
沒有，只是她工作能力比我強太多了
You guys, the drawing's about to start.
你們大家，快要開獎了
We should call my mom's and say good night to Emma..
我們應該打電話給我媽 跟艾□說晚安
- before she goes down. - Good idea.
-趕在她睡著以前 -好主意
Honey, you're being really strong about this.
親愛的，面對這件事你真的很堅強
I know how badly you wanted that job.
我知道你很想要這份工作
Yeah, you know, I really thought I deserved it.
是啊，你知道的 我真的以為這是該給我的
But let's go win the lottery. I mean, we still have a 130 chances to win, right?
讓我們來中樂透吧 我們還有一百三十個機會不是嗎？
Hundred and thirty-one.
一百三十一個
Yeah, good night, sweetheart. I love you.
是的，晚安甜心，我愛你
And remember, you're Daddy's little girl.
還有記住，你是爹地的小女孩
Phoebe's totally ruined that for me.
菲比完全毀了「爹地」
Hi, Mom. Put her back on.
嗨，媽，讓艾□聽
Rach, they're announcing the numbers!
瑞秋，他們在開獎了！
My God, I can already feel myself changing.
我的天啊，我可以感到自己在改變了
Here are your official Powerball numbers. We have 53.
這裡是正式超級大樂透中獎號碼 我們有五十三
- I've got that. - We have one too!
-我有 -我們也有一個！
We are on the road, people!
我們快中獎了！
Come on!
快點！
Mom, please, I know you love your new lips, but I can barely understand you.
媽，拜託，我知道你喜歡你的新嘴唇 但是我不太懂你在說什麼
Would you please just let me say good night to my daughter?
你可以讓我跟我女兒道晚安嗎？
And here we go. The Powerball is seven.
然後接下來的號碼是七
All right, check your numbers! Make me rich.
好了，你們快對號碼！ 讓我發財吧！
You guys, you're not gonna believe this.
你們大家，你們不會相信這個的
I was just saying good night to Emma, and she said her first words.
我剛剛在跟艾□說晚安的時候 她說了第一句話
- What? - Well, what did she say?
-什麼？ -那她說了什麼？
She said, "Gleba"!
她說了「葛利巴」！
Make me rich!
讓我發財吧！
- Isn't that amazing? - Oh, yeah. No, no, no, that's great.
-是不是很驚人呢？ -是啊，真是太棒了
Why aren't you more excited?
為什麼你沒有很興奮呢？
Rach, gleba is not a word.
瑞秋，葛利巴不算一句話
- Well, of course it is. - Okay. What does it mean?
-它當然算 -好吧，那它是什麼意思呢？
Well, I don't know all the words.
嗯，我又不認識所有的字詞
You know, I'm just glad I didn't miss my daughter's first word.
我只是很高興我沒有錯過 我女兒說第一句話
- Yes you did! Gleba is a word! - Okay. Use it in a sentence.
-你就是錯過了！葛利巴算！ -好的，那用它造句
Okay. Emma just said, "Gleba."
好的，艾□剛剛說了「葛利巴」
- It's not a word. - Okay, fine. I'm gonna look it up.
-那不算說話 -好的，我來查字典
Okay, great.
好的，太好了
While you're at it, she said another word the other day.
順便查一下 有天她也說了另外一句…
Why don't you look up:
你何不也查查看這個：
All right. Okay. Okay. Gleba. Gleba. Gleba. Gleba!
好了，葛利巴，葛利巴，葛利巴！
Here it is! "The fleshy, spore-bearing inner mass of a certain fungi."
找到了！「含孢子的豐厚菌種」
She's gonna be a scientist.
她會成為科學家的
- Damn it. Anybody got anything? - No.
-該死的，有人有對到嗎？ -沒有
I'm still looking through mine.
我還在對我的
Just double-checking. No.
再對一次，沒有
No. No.
沒有，沒有
No!
沒有！
Hello? Hold on.
哈囉？等一下
It's your boss.
是你老闆
The "I'm sorry I rejected you" phone call.
「很抱歉沒用你」的電話來了
I'm not used to getting these from guys.
我還真不習慣男生打這種電話來
- Hey, Steve. - Chandler, hi.
-嘿，史提夫 -錢德，嗨
I'm sure you've heard we filled the three positions.
我想你已經聽說我們三個名額都滿了
We felt that with your maturity and experience..
我們覺得以你的成熟度及經驗
you wouldn't be happy being someone's assistant.
你不會想要當助理的
I'd love to be somebody's assistant. Answering phones..
我愛死當助理了，接聽電話…
getting coffee, I live for that stuff.
倒咖啡，我就是為那些工作而活的
And I'm not too mature. Farts, boobies, butt cracks!
而且我並沒有很成熟 放屁、咪咪、屁蛋！
Chandler, you were the strongest person in the program.
錢德，你是全部的人裡面最優秀的
We're offering you the position of junior copywriter.
我們要聘請你當初級廣告文案
Me? That guy who just said, "butt cracks"?
我？那個剛剛才說「屁蛋」的人？
Yes, that's right.
是的，沒錯
We're excited about the level of sophistication..
我們很期望你能帶給這份工作…
you'll be bringing to the job.
一定程度的深度
Okay. Well, thanks, you won't regret it. I'll see you tomorrow.
好的，謝謝，你不會失望的 明天見
What?
怎樣？
Oh, yeah, I'm gonna be a junior copywriter.
對，我要當初級廣告文案了
Congratulations! Oh, sweetie, I'm so proud of you.
恭喜了！親愛的，我真以你為榮
Thanks. Does that mean I get the good loving tonight?
謝謝，這表示我今晚可以被愛愛嗎？
You bet. No TV or anything.
當然，不看電視或什麼其它的
- Hey, that is so great about the job. - Thanks, man.
-嘿，恭喜你找到工作了 -謝了，老兄
I'd like to think I had something to do with it.
我其實也有幫到忙
- Really? Why? - Well, before with the wishbone.
-真的嗎？怎麼說？ -剛剛在玩幸福骨頭的時候…
I didn't wish we would win the lottery. I wished you'd get the job.
我沒有許願我們中樂透 我許的願是你找到工作
Oh, yeah?
喔，是嗎？
Listen, don't tell Monica. She'll rip your heart right out.
聽著，別告訴摩妮卡 她會把你的心臟挖出來的
Well, you know what? There was a little part of me..
你們知道嗎？我一直有一點點感覺
that really thought we were gonna win.
覺得我們好像真的會中獎
Me too. So much for my dinosaur/Amelia Earhart theme park.
我也是，都是為了我的恐龍與 女飛行員主題公園
You guys? What was the Powerball number again?
特別號碼是多少？
- Seven. - We won.
-七 -我們中獎了
- What? - We won!
-什麼？ -我們中獎了！
- Let me see! Let me see! - Don't tear it!
-讓我看，讓我看 -別撕掉了
Phoebe, you don't have any of the first five numbers!
菲比，你其它五個號碼都不對！
I know that, but look, we got the Powerball number. We won $3!
我知道，但是我們中了特別號 我們中了三塊錢！
Wow, you think we should get that over 20 years or go for the big payout?
哇，你覺得我們應該分二十年提領 還是一次領光呢？
I don't care. I've never won anything before. I can't believe this!
我不管，我從來就沒有 中過任何東西，我真不敢相信！
So, Phoebe, what are you gonna do with your $3?
菲比，你要怎麼運用這三塊錢呢？
Well, it's not all mine. We all get 50 cents.
又不是全都是我的 我們每個人都有五十分
You know what? You can have mine.
你知道嗎？我的份給你
- Me too. - Me too.
-我的也是 -我的也是
Me too.
我的也是
Well, I guess if everybody else is.
好吧，既然大家都要給你
（中央咖啡廳）
Hey, guys. So I just called the Powerball hot line.
嘿，我剛剛打電話給樂透公司
- Can you believe it? Nobody won. - I beg to differ.
-你們敢相信嗎？沒有人中獎耶 -我希望不是那樣
Maybe nobody won the jackpot, but there was this guy in here earlier..
或許沒有人中頭獎 但是稍早有個人在這裡…
and he found a ticket on the street right outside and won $10,000.
在外面撿到一張彩券 中了一萬塊錢
Again, don't blame the pretty lady.
不要再責怪漂亮小姐了
It was not her fault. It was me, the pigeon.
那不是她的錯，是鴿子我的錯
Seriously, stop staring at her.
真的，不要再瞪她了